Weinberger Performing Arts Program Collection, 1947-2001
University of Houston Libraries
Weinberger Performing Arts Program Collection
1947-2001
Weinberger, Robert
2002-001
11 boxes; 11.5 linear feet
Performing arts programs, ticket stubs, and clipped reviews collected by Mr. Weinberger from 1947 through 2001. The programs reflect a variety of performance types and venues.
Special Collections, University of Houston Libraries
Biographical Note
Robert Weinberger was born and reared in New York City and began attending performing arts events and collecting programs in 1947. During this period there were special performances made available to high school students for ten cents a seat. He moved to Houston in 1965 and continued to attend cultural events here while frequently making trips to New York and abroad.
Scope and Contents
The collection contains drama, dance, opera, and symphony programs from performances given in North America and Europe. The programs are arranged chronologically from 1947 to 2001 and are housed in sixty-three binders. Ticket stubs and review clippings are attached to most of the programs with a few bearing autographs.
Subjects (Persons)
Weinberger, Robert
Formats
Programs
Acquisition Information
This collection was donated to the University of Houston in 2002.
Access Restrictions
Open for research.
Detailed Description
- Program Binders
  - November 1947 to December 1950 (Box 1, Binder 1)
  - December 1950 to February 1952 (Box 1, Binder 2)
  - June 1952 to June 1953 (Box 1, Binder 3)
  - June 1953 to January 1955 (Box 1, Binder 4)
  - January 1955 to January 1956 (Box 1, Binder 5)
  - February 1956 to December 1957 (Box 1, Binder 6)
  - December 1957 to September 1959 (Box 1, Binder 7)
  - September 1959 to August 1961 (Box 2, Binder 8)
  - August 1961 to August of 1962 (Box 2, Binder 9)
  - August 1962 to November 1963 (Box 2, Binder 10)
  - January 1964 to November 1964 (Box 2, Binder 11)
  - December 1964 to January 1966 (Box 2, Binder 12)
  - January 1966 to January 1967 (Box 2, Binder 13)
  - January 1967 to June 1968 (Box 2, Binder 14)
  - July 1968 to January 1969 (Box 3, Binder 15)
  - March 1969 to June 1970 (Box 3, Binder 16)
  - July 1970 to March 1972 (Box 3, Binder 17)
  - May 1972 to April 1973 (Box 3, Binder 18)
  - June 1973 to March 1974 (Box 3, Binder 19)
  - May 1974 to December 1974 (Box 4, Binder 20)
  - January 1975 to November 1975 (Box 4, Binder 21)
  - December 1975 to February 1976 (Box 4, Binder 22)
  - February 1976 to April 1977 (Box 4, Binder 23)
  - September 1977 to March 1978 (Box 4, Binder 24)
  - April 1978 to March 1979 (Box 5, Binder 25)
  - March 1979 to December 1979 (Box 5, Binder 26)
  - January 1980 to October 1980 (Box 5, Binder 27)
  - December 1980 to December 1981 (Box 6, Binder 28)
  - January 1982 to October 1982 (Box 6, Binder 29)
  - October 1982 to April 1983 (Box 6, Binder 30)
  - January 1984 to October 1984 (Box 7, Binder 31)
  - October 1984 to July 1985 (Box 7, Binder 32)
  - July 1985 to January 1986 (Box 7, Binder 33)
  - January 1986 to July 1986 (Box 7, Binder 34)
  - July 1986 to December 1986 (Box 7, Binder 35)
  - January 1987 to June 1987 (Box 8, Binder 36)
  - July 1987 to December 1987 (Box 8, Binder 37)
  - January 1988 to September 1988 (Box 8, Binder 38)
  - October 1988 to January 1990 (Box 8, Binder 39)
  - January 1990 to November 1990 (Box 8, Binder 40)
  - January 1991 to November 1991 (Box 9, Binder 41)
  - January 1992 to September 1992 (Box 9, Binder 42)
  - September 1992 to March 1993 (Box 9, Binder 43)
  - April 1993 to October 1993 (Box 9, Binder 44)
  - November 1993 to March 1994 (Box 9, Binder 45)
  - March 1994 to October 1994 (Box 10, Binder 46)
  - November 1994 to February 1995 (Box 10, Binder 47)
  - March 1995 to June 1995 (Box 10, Binder 48)
  - July 1995 to November 1995 (Box 10, Binder 49)
  - November 1995 to April 1996 (Box 10, Binder 50)
  - April 1996 to November 1996 (Box 10, Binder 51)
  - November 1996 to March 1997 (Box 10, Binder 52)
  - March 1997 to July 1997 (Box 10, Binder 53)
  - September 1997 to February 1998 (Box 10, Binder 54)
  - March 1998 to July 1998 (Box 11, Binder 55)
  - August 1998 to January 1999 (Box 11, Binder 56)
  - January 1999 to May 1999 (Box 11, Binder 57)
  - May 1999 to December 1999 (Box 11, Binder 58)
  - January 2000 to April 2000 (Box 11, Binder 59)
  - April 2000 to November 2000 (Box 11, Binder 60)
  - November 2000 to January 2001 (Box 11, Binder 61)
  - February 2001 to June 2001 (Box 11, Binder 61a)
  - July 2001 to November 2001 (Box 11, Binder 62)